# **JAQUELINE BIANCO**

#### JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Monte de Caparica, Almada, Portugal jaquezubieta@gmail.com +351 939 694 917









### **SUMMARY**

Brazilian based in Portugal. I'm graduated in Marketing and Advertising since 2019. I have six years of experience in digital marketing, specifically in SEO and Data Analytics. I've worked in several multidisciplinary teams and projects of major brands in brazilian market such as Volvo, O Boticário, Porto Seguro and Arezzo.

I'm currently on a career transition to development area. My goal is to become a Software Developer.

LANGUAGES	
Portuguese English Spanish	

### **SOFT SKILLS**

Organisation Time management
Team work Flexibility

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

JavaScript CSS/HTML CSS/HTML Version Control

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor's degree, Marketing and Advertising Universidade Tuiuti do Paraná, Curitiba, Brazil 2016 - 2019

## **SHORT COURSES**

Developer Training Path - RockseatIn progressFront-end Certification - AluraIn progressProgramming Logic - AluraComplete

I'm also learning from Youtube videos, personal projects and bootcamps. I share my projects on my Github!

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Mirum Agency Brazil - Curitiba, Paraná, Brazil.

Apr, 2021 - Jan, 2022

- · Audit of measurement tools to identify tracking improvements for datadriven decision making.
- Follow up with the API development for media platforms next to the DataOps team.
- · Dashboard development in DataStudio, connecting data sources such as GA and BigQuery

## **SEO Analyst**

**Data Analyst** 

Apr, 2018 - Feb, 2021

- Set SEO best practices for e-commerces and institutional websites.
- Track technical improvements such as indexability, pagespeed metrics and accessibility features.
- · Keyword research and market analysis.

#### **SEO Intern**

Jun, 2017 - Apr, 2018

Bluefoot Agency - Curitiba, Paraná, Brazil.

- Set organic acquisition strategies for latam e-commerces.
- · Track and report organic performance to stakeholders